Viewers all over the world, have faith in God.
Our heart is of faith; have faith in God.
Our heart is of faith.
Right now, heart to heart, viewers all over the world - heart to heart.
Receive a free spirit, in the name of Jesus.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In God's Word, there is deliverance.
There is blessing and breakthrough in God's Word.
Receive a free spirit, in the name of Jesus!
Only a free spirit can attract the Spirit of God.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Whatever darkness in your life,
sickness, disease - that demon, misfortune -
I command that darkness to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people!
Darkness is misfortune.
That sickness, disease, setback, nightmare -
I command them in the name of Jesus - leave my people!
You must leave my people.
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Our heart is the prayer room, the temple of God
but today, it has become a conflict room between flesh and Spirit.
There is so much division - for and against.
"I will forgive; I will not forgive."
Receive a free spirit, in the name of Jesus!
I command that deliverance on you, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever chain satan might have used to connect you to himself,
chain of sickness, nightmare, setback, affliction -
be broken, in the name of Jesus!
I can hear chains falling.
You know the chain satan might have been using to connect you to himself -
disappointment - chain of disappointment.
When you are going this way, something drags you back.
Chain of disappointment,
chain of doubt,
chain of rejection,
chain of hatred,
be broken, in the name of Jesus!
I can hear chains falling.
Here is your future, here is your career; you are riding on someone else's career.
Chain of setback, stagnation, barrenness, affliction - be broken, in the name of Jesus!
I can hear chains falling!
Let me rejoice with you; I can hear chains falling.
Chain of disappointment, affliction, stagnation, joblessness - I can hear chains falling!
I can hear chains falling, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to rejoice! I can hear breakthrough!
Breakthrough!
What am I hearing?
What am I hearing from above?
Breakthrough!
Say, "Breakthrough!"
I can't hear you.
Breakthrough!
In your business, career, family, marriage -
breakthrough, in Jesus' name!
TT: Anonymous
RV: Mel Flowers 17/12/2018